

- **%** 01854886330
- 🔁 safayetcse@gmail.com
- 🔘 Kalabagan, Dhanmondi, Dhaka

Skills

- HTML
- css/scss
- Material UI
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS
- React
- UX Research
- User Persona
- UI Design
- Wireframing
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping
- Collaboration

Tools & Software

- VS Code
- nmp / yarn
- Git
- Figma / XD
- Illustrator
- Photoshop

Md. Safayet Hossain

Frontend Designer & UI/UX Designer

Career objective

As a UI/UX designer, I create digital products such as websites, dashboards, mobile apps and software by understanding and optimizing the user experience. I am very friendly, polite and like to do my job duties responsibly.

On the other hand, as a highly-skilled frontend developer, I use my coding skills and experience working with UX/UI teams to implement high-performance websites and web applications and provide responsive web design/RWD multi-device and all-platform user experiences.

Work Experience

UX/UI Designer

2022- Present Soft IT Care - Dhaka, Bangladesh

My responsibilities are UI design, UX problem solving, high quality web application using latest trends, Mobile Application and Dashboard work with complete user accessibility interface design work. I work in company like SAAS project Have done and given best solution.

40+ Website, Landing page, Dashboard, app & SAAS project Done.

Front End Designer

2015–2017 Sujan IT LTD – Dhaka, Bangladesh

I am working as a front end designer in a famous software company Sujanit Ltd. I have worked on web application, mobile app and dashboard. Used modern technologies like HTML5, CSS3, React, Bootstrap, JAVASCRIPT, Jquery for various projects FIGMA/XD UI design.

25+ Corporate Website, Personal Landing page,
Dashboard & SAAS Application.

Interpersonal Skills

- Quick Independent Learner
- Self-motive and Confident
- Good Team leader
- Excellent communication skills
- logical approach to work

Interests

- Playing Video Game
- Travel
- Cycling
- Playing Cricket
- Watching Football

Feature Project

First Automated E-Commerce / App

This e-commerce sales funnel is a single-vendor, multi-vendor e-commerce platform for clients with all types of products.

Single Landing Page Website

I have worked on all types of single product landing websites for sellers who need a website to sell their various products.

Restaurant website designed / App

It features a modern and elegant design that is sure to attract customers and provide them with a seamless browsing experience.

E-learning platform

We have created a range of e-learning platforms specifically designed for your education.

Accounting Modules Dashboard

Cash Management Dashboard Track income and expenses for business growth, add your employees to the business, set up multiple businesses, download PDF and Excel reports

Education

Daffodil International University

2017-2020

B.Sc. in Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA: 3.00 out of 4.00

CCN Polytechnic Institute

2012 - 2016

Diploma in Computer Engineering

CGPA: 3.23 out of 4.00

Sayedpur High School, Cumilla

2011 - 2012

SSC

CGPA: 3.95 out of 5.00

Portfolio

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/safayet95

Oribbble: https://dribbble.com/SafayetHossain

Behance: https://www.behance.net/safayethossain5